♪ BACK TO LIFE,
BACK TO REALITY ♪
♪ BACK TO THE HERE
AND NOW, YEAH ♪
♪ SHOW ME HOW DECIDE ♪
♪ WHAT YOU WANT FROM ME ♪
♪ TELL ME, MAYBE I
COULD BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ HOW EVER DO YOU WANT ME ♪
♪ HOW EVER DO YOU NEED ME ♪
♪ BACK TO LIFE, BACK
TO THE PRESENT TIME ♪
♪ BACK FROM A FANTASY, YES ♪
♪ TELL ME, NOW, TAKE
THE INITIATIVE ♪
♪ I'LL LEAVE IT IN YOUR
HANDS UNTIL YOU'RE READY ♪
♪ HOW EVER DO YOU WANT ME ♪
♪ HOW EVER DO YOU NEED ME ♪
♪ I LIVE AT THE
TOP OF THE BLOCK ♪
♪ NO MORE ROOM FOR
TROUBLE AND FUSS ♪
♪ NEED A CHANGE, A
POSITIVE CHANGE ♪
♪ LOOK, IT'S ME
WRITING ON THE WALL ♪
♪ HOW EVER DO YOU WANT ME ♪
♪ HOW EVER DO YOU NEED ME ♪
♪ HOW DO YOU WANT ME TO BE ♪
♪ BACK TO LIFE, BACK
TO THE DAY WE HAVE ♪
♪ LET'S END THIS FOOLISH GAME ♪
♪ HEAR ME OUT, DON'T
LET IT WASTE AWAY ♪
♪ MAKE UP YOUR MIND SO
I KNOW WHERE I STAND ♪
♪ HOW EVER DO YOU WANT ME ♪
♪ HOW EVER DO YOU NEED ME ♪